The Dirtiest Dancing Of Them All!
Salsa is a music, romance film directed by Boaz Davidson.
Fatherless barrio Puerto Rican Rico is a menial car mechanic by day, but lives for the nights, when he dances and dates hot
dancing girls, cockily convinced the title of Salsa king in fancy nightclub La Luna's upcoming contest is to be his.
He encourages his best friend, courteous gentleman Ken, to date his sister
Margarita so he gets a free hand with her flirtatious classmate Lola.
The reigning salsa queen Luna's interest in Rico as
dance-partner threatens his on-off relationship with Vicki.
More jealous trouble follows when Ken and Margarita fall in true love.
Rico, played by Robi Draco Rosa.
Ken, played by Rodney Harvey.
Rita, played by Magali Alvarado.
Luna, played by Miranda Garrison.
Lola, played by Moon Orona.
Vicki, played by Angela Alvarado.
Salsa is a 1988 romance film directed by Boaz Davidson and starring Robby
Rosa, Rodney Harvey, Angela Alvarado and Miranda Garrison.
The film, about Puerto Rican dancer Rico who decides to enter a salsa dancing contest, earned a nomination
for the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst New Star for Rosa at the 9th Golden Raspberry Awards.
The tone is emotional.